※ Floopily subtitled by marinoFromFrance. ※
※ ... using Aegisub 3.0.4. ※
(Music plays.)
(Music becomes ominous.)
(Music Stops. She exhales.)
(Exhales deeply.)
(Chime. Computer voice.) Incoming video call.(Chime)
(Computer voice.) Audio only.
Hello? Kate...
Come on, seriously...
I can't see you first thing in the morning
not even on your birthday ?
It's the last thing you wanna see,
trust me.
You've had enough trauma in your life.
Come on, birthday girl...
And I... We gonna call over, ok?
No, I'm not ready.
I'll see you at breakfeast, Weston.
(Music plays.)
9th of june 2067
21 years old today.
Most of the birthdays are celebrating
another year of life...
... and congratulating
you're making it another year.
An entire year.
Some of us in Colombus 7
don't make it to 21.
Something about their lungs not adjusting to the recycled air.
I've read a lot of what it was like growing upon Earth
I can only read and wonder.
I've never been there.
In the beginning...
.. our sun was created to give light...
... and life to the Earth on which we lived.
Our planet was just at right distance from the sun...
... sustaining an amazing diversity
of animals, plants...
... and people to populate it.
But...
... what once sustained our lives...
... was soon be the end of it.
When the Earth fell out of orbit...
... we tried to reset the planet
with the use of particles accelerators.
As a results,
wormholes were created throughout the galaxies.
Temperatures on Earth skyrocketed...
... beyond anything ever seen before.
All the water eventually evaporated.
Without water, all the plants died.
Without plants, all the animals died.
Before mankind dies as well,
seven ships made it off the surface.
That was 40 years ago.
Each ship went off in search
of another planet.
One that can support human life.
For 37 years we've searched in vain.
The only thing which gets me through it ?
The training.
(Strong music plays.)
(Ray gun shooting.)
We're under enemy fire !
How far to the checkpoint?
That's a hundred meters.
Covering.
(Bomb's timer beeping.)
Move it!
Move, move, move!
(Blast.)
(Ray guns shootings and blasts.)
Fifty meters up.
You're slowing us down, Foster!
You're moving too fast, not checking your flank!
Oh, you've had an heart attack
keeping up with me?
Aren't you the one always
saying that girls are equals?
Steady , Calder!
He turned out  the one
that falls under pressure.
You guys get sloppy down there.
(Voice on intercom) Calder, you're moving
way too fast.
(Voice on intercom) You've 2 minutes
to reach your objective.
(Voice on intercom) Be quick,
but be precise.
(Voice on intercom) 2 minutes.
Check your mags!
(Guns cockings.)
Allright everybody,
stick with me!
We'll make it.
Follow my lead.
(Laser gun shoot.)
I'll draw their fire!
Wait until they reload, make a run for it.
Don't be sacks! Spread out!
Just in a minute!
(Music plays.)
(Ray guns shootings.)
Where is it?
(Beeping.) I've the locator saying we're here.
Stay alert, ladies.
I see it. 20 meters...
(Ray guns shooting. Music playing.)
Contact link!
(Ray guns shootings.)
Exercise over.
Not bad.
See room for improvement but...
... not bad at all.
Training in the simulator is the closest thing
for me being off the ship.
I know it's not real.
But it's enough of a change to give me
something to look forward to each day.
I'll check your individual reports for your assessment.
Why all the training?
I think we will never use this.
Because we have to be ready.
Hey?
Err.. Ready for... Ah... What ?
For when we get off the ship.
(Chuckles.)
Ok, good luck with that.
Hey ! Just because he's my brother...
... it doesn't mean that you've to put up with him.
Hey ! Come on ! Let's move !
Hand in hand come back !
Let's go. (Music plays.)
(Fists hitting punching pads.)
All right !
Your turn. Pair up!
(Fists hitting punching pads.) One two three four...
One two three four...
One two ! Up ! Down !
One two ! Knee ! Knee !
Treat yourself.
All right ! All right !
That's enough !
Freestyle, 2 minutes.
You're one of the smallest ones out here.
Which means you're better off keeping him  close.
Use your knees, use your elbows.
You're leading way too much
with your arms.
Lead with your core.
(Fists hitting heavy bag.)
You just can't stand and criticize me.
(Chucling.) I didn't say anything.
You don't have to.
(Fists hitting heavy bag.)
Slow Is Smooth, Smooth Is Fast.
What's that supposed to mean?
Go slow and smooth.
(Fists hitting heavy bag.)
That's better, but even slower.
Good.
Improving slowing, precise repetition...
... create muscle memory
creating smooth motion...
... and once you're smooth,
... you can increase your speed.
(Fists hitting heavy bag.)
(Hitting faster.)
Good ! But be patient.
I don't like it when you call me out
in front of the others.
I only do so to make you stronger.
I promised your father
that I would make sure...
I don't need you to be my father!
Or my older brother.
What do you want me to be?
My captain.
(Fists hitting heavy bag.)
So. Hit me.
(Fists hitting punching pads.)
When are we going
to use a wormhole to travel?
Don't hold back to yourself.
Hit me!
(Breathing.)
We're dying up here and you know it.
It's our only chance to surviving.
Out of the question !
(Fists hitting. Breathing.)
We've haven't heard the other ships in years.
They can have made the jump already.
Yeah! And they ... could be dead too.
That's why the risk's worth it.
We're dying up here.
(Fists hitting. Breathing.)
Hands up ! Up !
(Heavy blow.) Ouch !
Keep your hands up.
That's better.
All right.
You'll really go for more ?
Look up. Point.
(Fists hitting. Breathing.)
(Him panting. Her chuckling.)
Light travels almost 300.000 km/s.
As far as we can tell...
... nothing in the physical universe can go faster.
But because light travels so fast...
... and because its speed is constant...
... we can use it to measure the incredible distances
in the universe.
Earth's nearest stellar neighbour
is Proxima Centauri.
It took light more than 4 years to reach Earth.
Light from the nearest galaxy, Andromeda,...
... travelled to Earth in about 2 million years
I've made it 21 so far.
The only way we will make it...
... is faster-than-light travel
through a wormhole.
(Music plays.)
(Elevator voice.)Deck 9.
Come, I'm not gonna say anything...
... and I'll act really surprised...
(Elevator voice.)Deck 8.
You just told me ... what's...
what's gonna happen...
(Elevator voice.)Deck 7.
Oh, we've arrived.
(Doors open.) Oh!
(Crowd chatters.) We're all down here.
We've been said to come in.
Hey ! Hey, did you hear what's up ?
(Computer voice.) Captain on deck.
(Indistinct chatter.)
Let's give you something to look at.
Some of you may have figured ou
that we are...
... Not too close to home.
At least what some of us once called home.
We are away on the boonies here.
Recently, we received a transmission...
... through a wormhole in the Hovant system.
What kind of transmission ?
From one of the other ships ?
No. Not from one of the ships.
From a planet, within the wormhole.
The signal is faint, but it is there.
It was you, wasn't it ? You discovered it, didn't you ?
This is our first contact in 37 years.
37 years on this cold tin cup of a ship.
For many of you, this is the
only home you've ever known.
We've been searching for an oportunity
like this for a long time.
We're goint into investigation.
(Music plays.)
We're sending a scout to the opening of the wormhole,
... held by myself and its light crew.
A list will be posted at hour 9:00.
Do we... catch on the list ?
This planet is inhabited.
It could be our new home.
(Chuckles.)
(Music plays louder then resumes.)
(Machinery clanking.)
Couch loop detached.
(Clickings.)
Hey captain.
Yes.
What's your favorite thing about Earth ?
The air.
Hmmm...
Better than this... recycled garbage
we're taking on our ship.
Describe it !
Clear.
No. Clean.
Especially after a rain.
(Electronic chirping.)
And this... smell after it.
(Voice on intercom.) The ocean... Fresh cut grass...
(Music plays louder.)
(Computer voice.) Entering wormhole.
Have you've ever riden an horse?
(Chuckling.) What ? Errr...
Yeah. Just once.
It was with your father actually.
(Voice on intercom) We could have been...
more than eleven.
(Voice on intercom) While walking
home from school one day...
(Voice on intercom) ... we roamed by this pasture, watched the horses,
... and your dad says "Hey why not we go in and...
ride one of them."
(Voice on intercom) We jumped over the fence.
(Voice on intercom) We walked up to each one's horse.
Your dad'd already jumped to his.
As fast as Pat may run, jumped upon her back...
(Chuckling.) ... and she... rose up on her...
(Voice on intercom) ... hind legs. He's just...
(Voice on intercom) ... He's got one hand holding ,
the other up in the air.
(Voice on intercom) He's laughing with a big smile on his face.
(Voice on intercom) He got her calm down.
He just jumped off and said "Hey, it's your turn."
(Computer voice.) Proximity alert.
Proximity alert.
Right, you've better hold on.
It's gonna get a little bumpy.
(Music plays louder.)
(Computer voice.) Danger incoming !
(Explosion noise.)
(Computer voice - indistinct.)
(Explosion noises.)
(Noises of debris scattering.)
(Loud noise.)
(Whistling wind.)
(Music plays.)
(Music plays louder.)
(Native language.) Father, come quick!
(Native language.) What's going on?
(Native language.) A body has fallen from the sky.
(Native language.) It has landed in the water, behind the hill.
(Ominous music plays.)
(Native language.) They've come again on our land.
(Native language.) We allow no outsiders !
(Native language.) They will be killed without exception !
(Native language.) Hold! We shoud not act so rashly !
(Native language.) You dare to oppose me ?
(Native language.) Don't you know where you belong ?
(Native language.) Death to outsiders !
(Subacquatic gurgling.)
(Breathing. Coughing)
(Subacquatic gurgling. Water splashes.)
(Waves splashes.)
(Panting.)
(Music plays.)
(Horse neighs.)
(Noises of hooves.)
(Supersonic bang.)
(Crash noise.)
(Loud music plays.)
(Panting.)
(Electronic chirping. Computer voice.) Initiating body scan.
(Computer voice.) Body scan complete.
(Computer voice.) Heart rate : 200.
(Computer voice.) BP : 125 over 85.
(Computer voice.) Life rate : 90 %.
Incoming video call.
Kate! We're taking on water. Help !
Kate? Can you hear me ?
Kate! Can you hear me ?
We... we need help !
Hayley, I'm coming !
(Computer voice.) Topography scanned.
(Computer voice.) Initializing tracking system.
(Computer voice.) Hayley Swindle located
one kilometer away.
(Loud music plays. Explosion noises.)
(Water splash.)
(Subacquatic gurgling.)
(Water splashes. Coughing.)
Hayley, stop !
(Subacquatic gurgling. Water splashes. Coughing.)
Your feet! (Water splashes. Coughing.)
(Subacquatic gurgling.)
(Water splashes. Coughing.)
What happened?
The ship went down.
No, no, no...
This is messed up.
I hard... hardly believe... This is... this is...
Hayley, we've got to get up!
We gotta go!
- Wait.
- Where is Weston ? Where's captain Hunter ?
(Slap soud.) Hayley !
Listen !
I know you're in shock,
... but we have to stand up,
and we have to call help!
All right?
(Exhales.)
(Screaming.) Kate !
(Crying.) Please help me !
(Panting.) Hayley...
Kate...
- Stop ! Stop !
(Crying.) - I don't know what to do...
Anne ?
- Anne ?
(Crying.) - I don't know what to do...
(Crying.) - I don't know...
- Keep pressure on the wound !
- Anne? Anne, can you hear me ?
(Crying.) - She's bleeding too much...
Hayley ! Hayley !
Will we tip her ?
(Crying.) Help !
(Exhales.)
(Crying.) - Will Anne be ok ?
- Anne ?
(Panting.)
(Coughing.)
Help !
- What happened ? Where are we?
- Anne ?
- It's ok, Anne, I'm... I'm here.
- What is that ?
It's like it is my blood... Weston,
tell me that's not my blood.
You need to breathe. So, Anne, you breathe.
Slow down, your breathing... Slow down... Good.
I need to see what happened.  That way, I may help you.
Anne ? Anne ? I need to look
and see what happened.
(Wet noise. Cries of pain.)
Keep pressure on the wound !
(Cries of pain.)
- Anne ?
(Cries of pain.) - What ?
You're gonna die.
(Crying.) Wait... There's gotta be something we can do !
There's gotta be something we can do !
(Crying.) - There's gotta be ...
- Stop ! ... Weston !
Anne ? Anne ?
Hey, Anne, look at me, ok ?
Anne ?
Hey, look at me... It's ok.
- Anne ? Anne ?
(Crying.)- Is she... Is she dead ?
(Crying.) She can't be dead, ok...
She... She can't be dead, ok...
(Crying.) She can't be dead... really...
We've got to do something...
(Crying.)
(music plays. Indistinct sobbing.)
Oxygen levels are high...
Gravity normal.
(Music plays.)
Kate ? ... Kate !
Hay... Give me a minute.
The distress signal is no longer active.
What does that mean ?
What do we do ?
(Crying.) I'm sorry, Anne.
(Panting.)
(Waves splashing.)
(Ominous sound.)
(Shooting. Crowd screaming.)
(Moaning.)
(Noisy breathing.)
(Shooting.)
(Slow creepy music plays.)
(Grunting.)
(Exhales.)
(Faint grunting.)
(Grunting.)
(Electronic chirping.) Weston ? Hayley ?
Does anybody hear me ?
(Loud music playing.)
Does anybody receive me ?
Please respond.
(Computer voice.) Incoming video call.
(Voice on radio.) Hailing frequencies. Respond.
Captain, it's Kate.
Where are you ?
(Voice on radio.) Oh, Kate. Thanks God you're still alive.
Anne's dead.
It's my fault. I'm the one
that called her on the ship.
It's not your fault.
Kate... If there's any blame here...
... it falls on me.
Have you been able to reach any of the others ?
(Sigh.) No.
(Voice on radio.) I saw some survive the crash.
(Voice on radio.) Weston, Hayley and few others, but...
... we're not alone here.
- We were attacked and I was taken.
(Voice on radio.)  By who ?
Indigenous lifeform. Two kinds. One...
... one very human, but very animalistic
and... and savage.
The others were monsters, beasts...
(Voice on radio.) Obviously, you escaped. You ok?
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
(Voice on radio.) You've done a...
topography scan?
For some land but... just when I was trying
to locate Haysley.
(Voice on radio.)  I will send you ... what I have.
(Voice on radio.) You should be able
to see my location.
(Electronic chirping.) Coming through.
(Electronic chirping.) Analyzing.
(Electronic chirping.) Joining.
We are connected, but ...
... it's not all there.
Your vitals...
(Voice on radio.)  They were never that good...
to begin one.
- What's broken ?
(Voice on radio.) Look, I'm fine.
What's broken ?
(Voice on radio.) - My leg.
- How bad is it ?
(Voice on radio.) Well... Unlikely I will be able to the tango floor.
(Electronic chirping.) You're sixty kilometers away from me.
(Voice on radio.)Right.  Check one more time to get the data.
(Voice on radio.) I marked a section where the ship is.
(Voice on radio.) It's still intact. There should be a medic pack
and a distress beacon.
Were you able to locate the transmission
that sent us here in the first plac e?
(Voice on radio.) Yeah. You know we lost it
since we came through the wormhole.
What do you mean me to do ?
(Voice on radio.) You get to me first and then,
between you and the ship...
(Voice on radio.) ... is a...
(Voice on radio.) ... pretty rough terrain for you to cover, so...
(Voice on radio.) Be smart. It can take you a couple of day to get here.
(Voice on radio.) I imagine also... that you got pretty tired
and hungry since last time you ate.
Err... I don't know.
(Voice on radio.) Use your scanner. Find edible plants.
You need...
(Voice on radio.) ... to set up,
(Voice on radio.) ... camp the night and have a good rest.
You can...
(Voice on radio.) ... get up for soon in the morning.
(Computer voice.) Initializing scan.
(Computer voice.) Plant unedible..
(Ominous music plays.)
(Pouring rain and thunder.)
(Distant roaring
(Computer voice.) Captain Hunters vitals:
(Computer voice.) Heart rate : 32,
(Computer voice.) BP :  83 over 45,
(Computer voice.) Life rate : 65 %.
(Loud music plays.)
(Ominous music plays.)
(Breathes heavily.)
(Native language.) See how many of us were killed !
(Native language.) You are not fit to lead us !
(Native language.) I've saved our lives !
(Native language.) I have done what had to be done !
(Native language.) Not all your decisions are good.
(Native language.) Obey or die !
(Panting. Rocks falling. Shooting.)
(Native language.) Kill her !
(Loud music plays.)
(Panting.)
(Calling in native language.)
(Breathes heavily.)
(Native language.) Stay still ! I do not want to hurt you !
(Loud music plays.)
(Breathes heavily.)
(Native language.) Rogan, come here !
(Groans.)
(Exhales.)
(Blades noises.)
(Gun cocking.)
(Loud music plays.)
(Computer voice.) 56 kilometers to objective.
(Computer voice.) Estimated time : 2 days.
(Computer voice.) Captain Hunter's life rate : 43 %.
(Computer voice.) Quickest route is straight up.
(Loud music plays.)
It's taking too long.
I didn't make far enough today.
(Voice on radio.) You're safe.
Yes.
How are you doing ?
(Voice on radio.) Be honest, Hunter.
You know err... not good.
(Voice on radio.) I stopped the bleeding.
(Voice on radio.) But I've lost a lot of blood,
and my leg's in...
(Voice on radio.) ... pretty bad shape...
(Voice on radio.) I'm fine...
(Voice on radio.) Hard to breathe now too.
I'm still over 48 kilometers away.
I don't know if I make it on time.
(Voice on radio.) One of the... greatest weaknesses
of most of us...
(Voice on radio.) ... is the lack of faith.
(Voice on radio.) I believe in you, Kate.
(Voice on radio.) Don't worry about me. I... I'll hold on.
(Voice on radio.) Get some rest. You... You make up for tomorow.
Good night, Captain.
(Voice on radio.) Good night.
(Exhales.)
(Computer voice.) Still 49 kilometers to objective.
Estimated time :  47 hours.
(Animal shrieking. Computer voice.) Captain Hunter's life rate : 39 %.
(Animal shriekings.)
(Neighings.)
(Neighings. Gruntings.)
(Thump.)
(Neighing.)
(Soft music plays.)
(Music plays louder.)
(Soud of hooves.)
(Computer voice.) 15 kilometers to destination.
Captain Hunter's life rate : 33 %.
(Music plays louder.)
(Computer voice.) 1 kilometers to destination.
Captain! ... Captain!
Hey Kate! I knew you'd made it.
You don't look so good.
Thanks.
Let's take a look.
(Computer voice.) Initializing body scan.
Sorry about this.
Dreaming your whole life but setting foot on a planet...
and this is what you end up with.
(Computer voice.)  Analyse is complete.
(Electronic chirping.)
The break is not all the way through...
... and your lacerations
are'nt too serious.
(Electronic chirping.)
Got a broken rib that's punctured a lung.
Hu... That explains why it's so hard to breathe.
Kate, you've to ... get to the ship
to get that medic pack.
Yes.
And get the salvage ship
just bring in the main ship.
That sound.
A horse.
A horse... On this planet...
And you rode it here.
Yeah. She saved me. I saved her.
(Breathing painfully.) Yeah.
Did you have
to kill anyone else ?
No.
(Breathing painfully.)  When the ... ship gets here, we'll...
we'll be able to ... search for them.
We've better get going.
The rocket is only 13 kilometers away, but...
... the terrain is pretty severe.
I will take care of the horse.
Well, I'll watch her.
Sorry for all this , Kate.
Be careful.
(Loud music plays.)
(Roaring.)
(Roaring. Loud music plays.)
(Roarings.)
I've made it.
(Voice on radio.) It's good, Kate. It's good...
(Voice on radio.) Get yourself to the highest point
you can see and activate it.
Got it.
(Music plays.)
(Electronic chirping.) I've made it.
Activating distress beacon now.
(Electronic chirping. Computer voice.)  Acquiring signal.
Distress beacon activated.
(Rocket sound.)
(Voice on radio.) Good job. Get yourself back here.
(Voice on radio.) Bring the medic pack with you.
I'm on my way.
(Electronic chirping. )
Captain...
The signal we were following before's been activated.
I don't undestand.
(Voice on radio.) Kate... You know where we are now...
(Breathes heavily.) The only explanation...
(Loud noise.) Captain !
(Electronic chirping. )
(Loud music plays.)
(Electronic chirping. Computer voice.) Tracking captain Hunter. Heat signature nearby.
(Music plays.)
(Gruntings.)
(Roaring.)
(Gruntings. Blade sound.)
(Panting.)
Captain? ... Captain, you there ?
Go ahead. Just kill me.
(Distorted voice.) You're speaking the ancient tongue.
(Soft music plays.)
- I need your help.
- What did you do to my friends ?
I know where your friends are.
I'm called Rogan.
We can help each other.
Where are my friends?
You let me bleed out
and you will never know what happened to them.
Fine
So you talk.
(Panting with pain.)
Can you stich ?
What ?
Stich, with a needle.
Why would I help you ?
Because if you don't ...
your friends will almost likely die.
(Moans with pain.)
You attacked us without warning.
We had no chance.
No.
Some from my tribe will have nothing to do with outsiders.
I tried to stop them.
How many are you ?
A tribe of several hundreds.
I'm part of a scavenger party. I...
... look for others believing
that not all outsiders are bringing harm.
Why were you following me ?
Djavul has my dauther.
These creatures ?
They took your friends as well.
And they took you.
But you escaped.
It gives me hope that my daughter is still alive.
(Soft music plays.)
Why don't they kill right away ?
They feast slowly.
They have hunted and killed my people
for all back as I can remember.
You're the only one I know
who has ever escaped alive.
You must take me there.
How old is you daughter ?
Nidal.
She is nine.
She's all I have.
Why should I trust you ?
(Neighings.)
You trust my horse
but you don't trust me ?
She's your horse ?
Well, she's mine now.
(Loud music plays.)
I we're in such a hurry,
then why are we stopping ?
The horse needs to rest.
We can leave her
and continue on foot...
... or wait for and then travel faster.
Sorry... about that.
Where's the girl's mother ?
Killed by the Djavul
when Nidal was very young.
Djavul ?
It means "demon".
They were not always so.
Nearly 400 years ago, it was...
... no longer possible to live on the planet's surface.
Seven vessels left Earth,
with the promise that one day they would return.
Those who were left behind moved...
... deep under the planet's surface
where they remained for over a hundred years.
One group returned to the surface and found it livable.
The rest rather...
... remain in the groud and...
... over the years changed
into something that was no longer human.
What year is it ?
The year is 2452.
Yes, this is Earth.
You are from one
of the seven vessel, don't you ?
(Loud music plays.)
My com has records of my path
It'll show us the way.
(Roaring.)
(Roaring. Cries of pain.)
- Hayley ?
- Kate !
- Hayley ? Hayley ?
Hello. I like to see you again.
(Blade sound.)
What is he doing here, hu?
You killed our people.
- You killed our people...
- He's here to help.
- Kate, ... don't go...
- I'm not going anywhere. I'm not going anywhere.
(Crying.) They tore them apart and...
there were nothing I could do...
... I just did sat and watch,
and there was nothing I could do...
Weston, keep it together !
Have you seen a small child ? A young girl ?
He's looking for his daughter.
We heard screams.
They didn't sound
as if they came from a small child.
(Fainly.) Really... I...
(Coughing.)
I... I couldn't do any... any...
I couldn't do... I tried to stop... I... I...
There was nothing you could do.
That's right... I did... I couldn't do anything...
You've always been...
a real dumb-ass, Weston.
Hayley ?
Hayley ? No, no ! Hayley ?
Hayley ? Hey ! Hey !
Hayley ?
I'm sorry.
Your captain's still alive.
I'm sorry, Hayley.
(Electric zap. Yells of pain.) Oh, that hurts !
I reset the bone in your leg.
Oh.  (Panting with pain.) Oh.
I'm glad to see you.
Damned...
How many of us are left ?
You, Weston and myself.
(Exhales.)
Who's this ?
It's Rogan.
He's from this planet.
- Captain, this is Earth.
- Yeah.
The year is 2452.
2452...
All right.
You and Weston,
you'd better get out of here.
I'm in no condition to move.
Go to the distress beacon.
Contact the ship.
He's ri... he's right.
We got to get out of here.
I don't know how many are there, but...
- ... they are coming.
- No, I'm not leaving you behind.
What... what we can do with Hayley ?
We can't carry her ?
Weston is right.
Just leave me here with Hayley.
I did not come all this way
just to leave you behind.
(Yells with pain.) Ouch !
What was that ?
- I gave you a shot of adrenalyn.
It's meant to get you up. Get up !
Ouch !
She was here.
There's still hope.
We're not gonna leave Hayley's body here
for they would disgrace it.
(Music plays.)
Let's move slow. Don't rush it.
How are you holding up?
Well, if you're asking me about one other shot,...
... no thanks. I'm fine.
Nidal !
(Loud.) Nidal !
- You can lead them to us.
- I came for my daughter.
Stay out of my way.
Rogan, I've an idea.
The comp has already scanned the area.
Also had a look for the heat signals.
- Ok, that might be her.
- Which way ?
That way.
Nidal !
(Native language.) Father.
(Native language.) Come out. It's all right.
(Sigh. Soft music plays.)
(Native language.) You are such a brave strong girl.
(Native language.) They've killed so many of us, father.
(Native language.) I didn't know how to help them.
I wanted to.
(Native language.) I stayed hidden like you taught me to.
(Native language.) You're alive. That's the only important thing.
(Native language.) You must be hungry.
This is Kate.
She brought me here.
And we have to help them.
They are from one of the seven vessels.
(Shrieking.)
(Whispering.) Stay behind me.
(Roaring.)
(Grunting.)
(Ominous music plays. Gruntings.)
Ouch !
(Roarings.)
(Rumblings.)
Nidal !
- Nidal ! Kate !
(Native language.) - Father ! Father !
(Coughings.) We're here !
Kate !
- Captain !
- Get your hand away and lemme see.
- We're ok ! We're ok !
(Coughings.) Dad ?
(Coughings.) It's not that bad
Your arterie wasn't torn.
- All right. You'll be ok.
- I know. I know.
- Stay away from me.
- Leap out.
- No, no, no...
- You guys are ok in there ?
- Weston is up and we'll make it.
Don't hurt me.
We won't be able to move these rocks.
You take Nidal and get out.
Weston and I will find another way.
No. We can't split up!
We don't have a choice.
Get them up !
(Coughings.)
Meet you on the surface !
Come on.
It's up this way.
- Come on !
- Just let me there.
- Come on ! Come on ! Get up !
- Hold on !
- What will that be ?
- See what ?
- Get quiet ! Quiet !
- This way.
- Ok, you go first.
I'm ok.
Come on.
(Breathes painfully.)
You're still behind me ?
There... Still here.
Keep moving.
- Hold up.
- What is it ?
Djavul...
(Roarings.)
It's not going to be easy.
(Roaring.)
Captain ?
(Gruntings.)
Well, it's not like if we have much of a choice.
Just stand and fight.
(Breathes painfully.)
(Roarings.) It's behind me. It is right behind me.
Keep moving ! Don't stop !
Come on, Weston !
(Roarings.) It has my leg !
Give me your hand !
- Help me !
- Keep moving !
- Please !
Hey... We're good.
We've changed tunnel.
Let's move.
(coughing.)
(Loud music plays. Shriekings.))
Weston! Are you ok ? Are you all right ?
(Thud.)
Come... Weston... Sit down...
(Groanings.)
We'll clear path. Thake the girl
and make a run for it.
We'll fight together.
- Get out of there it's an order.
- I'm not leaving. I've already lost one dad.
You get out and you see to lock this cave.
I'm not leaving.
- You so stubborn !
- Yes, I've learned from the best.
(Roaring.)
All right. Do give me another shoot of adrenalyn.
Ouch ! God, well, that hurts !
(Roarings.)
Ok... Go ! Go ! Go !
Hold on ! Stay with me,
all right ? Stay with me.
Stay awake. We'll make it.
Ouch !
(Music plays. Roarings.)
Kate !
(Nidal shrieking.) Did you hear that ?
They are close. Come on !
Kill it !
(Loud music plays. Roarings.)
You're ok ?
(Breathes painfully.)
Hey !
Are you ok ?
What... What did I miss ?
We made it.
I'm the only one.
You stick with me, and it's going smooth...
(Nidal cries. Ominous music plays.)
(Native language.) Are you willing to sacrify the life
of your daughter for the outsiders?
(Native language.) This woman led me to Nidal.
(Native language.) - She saved her life !
(Native language.) - You know the law !
(Native language.) All outsiders must die.
(Native language.) We've always abided by it, without exception.
(Native language.) The law is wrong.
(Native language.) I will not let you endanger our people.
(Native language.) They will die today !
(Native language.) If it's your choice, do join them.
(Roarings. Shriekings.)
(Native language.) Your stupidity...
(Native language.) ... will kill to us all!
(Explosion sound.)
(Native language.) Will you at last lower your weapons?
(Native language.) Let us get back where we belong in peace !
(Native language.) The spaceships are coming back.
(Native language.) There's hope !
(Crowd cheering. Music plays.)
(Explosion sound.)
(Soft music plays.)
Dad ! Kate !
What is it ?
Come with me !
(Music plays.)
※ Movie's over, folks. ※
※ I apologize for the inevitable
and unforgivable mistakes. ※